<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Developer Jobs</string>
    <string name="contoh_description"><p>Who we are</p>\n\n
        <p>LiGr systems is a growing startup in the sports and media tech industry which creates automated,
            real-time data-driven graphic displays (scoreboards, team lists, infographics) for sports organisations
            from grassroots to professional for use primarily over live video broadcasts.</p>\n\n
        <p>Who we're looking for:</p>\n\n
        <p>This is a unique opportunity to build exciting, bleeding edge technology in the sports and broadcast industry,
            and we are looking for a talented, experienced javascript/web engineer to join our team and help build
            on our ideas. </p>\n\n
        <p>The successful applicant will be able to assist us in meeting the challenges of scale as we expand our
            operation internationally. You will have an immediate opportunity to influence the product strategy
            and organisational culture. </p>\n\n
        <p>Successful candidates will be invited to meet our leadership
            team in person or over video chat.</p>\n\n
        <p>The following skills are required</p>\n\n
        <p>Strong engineering ability, \nFluent / Advanced English, \nExcellent practical problem-solving, \nA
            passion for software, \nGreat written communication skills, \nOrganisational skills, \nContinuous Learner,
            \nAbility to work unsupervised</p>\n\n<p>The following skills are highly valued</p>\n\n
        <p>Cloud infrastructure e.g. containers(docker), Kubernetes, GCP, cloud functions,\nReact, webpack, babel, r
            edux\nSvg, gsap, animation/motion graphics\nEvent-driven architectures, event sourcing,\nTesting
            unit/integration/e2e/CI/CD,\nUnderstanding of design systems,\nCSS</p>\n\n
        <p>The following is also valued</p>\n\n
        <p>Some understanding of sport,\nVideo streaming - encoding/hls/rtmp/storage/facebook/youtube</p>\n\n
        <p>Our current stack:</p>\n\n<p>React,\nNode.js,\nDocker,\nKubernetes,\nGCP,\nGoogle Firestore</p>\n\n
        <p>What you”ll be doing</p>\n\n
        <p>Creating web interfaces/content management systems, \nImplementing graphic components,
            \nImproving event-driven architecture and building backend services</p>\n\n
        <p>Benefits of the role</p>\n\n
        <p>In addition to being a part of a great team, working in a fun and creative environment and learning
            from the best technical minds in the sports industry, we offer:</p>\n\n<p>Competitive salary, \nAccess to the
            latest tools and technologies, \nWork with global sporting bodies and sports leagues, \nRemote work with a virtual
            and regular communication environment (Trello, Slack, Github etc), \nStart-up sized company, where you can make an
            immediate impact, \nBuild software that will have a global impact on sports and the future of sports broadcast, \nOur
            team is technical and understands developer needs</p>\n\n
        <p>Apply</p>\n\n
        <p>Applying is easy. Send an email with your resume, website, Github account, links to apps or anything else you're proud
            of. If we like what we see, we’ll get in touch and organise a catchup in person or over video chat. We’ll then tell
            you more about the role and we can decide if there's a fit.</p>\n\n
        <p>Email applications to <a href="mailto:luke@ligrsystems.com">luke@ligrsystems.com</a></p>"</string>
    <string name="contoh_howto"><p>Please apply through our web app form at  <a href="https://www.janestreet.com/join-jane-street/apply/\">https://www.janestreet.com/join-jane-street/apply/</a></p></string>
</resources>
